{
    "subject": "resource/Akira_Tohei",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/givenName",
    "object": "Akira",
    "human_readable": "The given name of Akira Tohei is Akira.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9871917963027954,
            "question": "Is Akira Tohei's given name Akira?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9829494953155518,
            "question": "What is the given name of Akira Tohei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9472232460975647,
            "question": "Who is Akira Tohei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9318459033966064,
            "question": "Does Akira Tohei have a different name besides Akira?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9184650778770447,
            "question": "What is the first name of Akira Tohei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8767532706260681,
            "question": "How would you refer to Akira Tohei formally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8480291962623596,
            "question": "Is 'Akira' a common given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7944464683532715,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Akira Tohei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7611297369003296,
            "question": "What is the significance of the name 'Akira'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.707169234752655,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Akira Tohei?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The given name of Akira Tohei is Akira.",
            "html": "dbpedia_655_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the name 'Akira'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_655_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about Akira Tohei?",
            "html": "dbpedia_655_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Akira' a common given name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_655_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_655_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents clearly state that the full name of the person being discussed is \"Akira Tohei\", which supports the triple that the given name of Akira Tohei is indeed \"Akira\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that the person being discussed is named \"Akira Tohei,\" which confirms that his given name is indeed \"Akira.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}